[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '色んな' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "いろんな"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '旅' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "たび"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '葉っぱ' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "はっぱ"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji '生け花' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "いけばな"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '焼き芋' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "やきいも"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '用事' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ようじ"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '宿題' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しゅくだい"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '大変' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "たいへん"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji 'バス停' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "バスてい"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '門番' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "もんばん"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the kanji '並びます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ならびます"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the kanji '国立' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "こくりつ"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the kanji '例えば' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "たとえば"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the kanji '授業' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "じゅぎょう"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the kanji '簡単(な）' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かんたん"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the kanji 'お菓子' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おかし"
    }
]